

Kansas City, MO 64112 (913) 620-3091 nickdunn2@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Senior software engineer and team lead specializing in JavaScript (both front-end and back-end). With 7+ years of experience, I've led a wide variety of teams and solved an even wider variety of problems. I love clean, readable, tested code, and I appreciate collaborating with others who like to dig in and solve challenging problems. Awarded "Top 20% Performer" at FloSports four separate years and anxious for a new challenge!

SKILLS

- · JavaScript, TypeScript
- Node, NestJS, Redis, SDUI
- Angular, React, Next
- Git, CI/CD, Segment, Stripe
- · Jest, Cypress, A/B Testing
- · Communication, Leadership

EXPERIENCE

DECEMBER 2020-CURRENT Senior Software Engineer FloSports | Austin, Texas

- Technical lead on multiple, widely varying teams.
- Lead contributor on a NestJS "back-end for front-end" microservice, utilizing server-driven UI concepts to build out features for TV (Roku, AppleTV, FireTV), mobile (iOS, Android) and web clients.
- Boosted FloSports subscriber revenue and retention by executing dozens of successful A/B experiments.
- Overhauled navigation from back-end to front-end for both web and mobile apps to reduce friction for users trying to find one of FloSports' millions of pieces of content.
- Increased page views and fan engagement by creating full-stack sports data pipeline to power cheerleading results and standings using Salesforce, Firestore, NestJS & Angular.
- Served, monitored & supported public, high-traffic, low-latency web applications at edge with Fastly, Redis and DataDog.
- Helped company scale by engaging in security efforts to detect and block nefarious actors against 25 different web sites, reducing outages.

AUGUST 2016-DECEMBER 2020 Software Engineer FloSports | Austin, Texas

- Started in August 2016 as a junior developer fresh out of a coding bootcamp and internship.
- By January 2018, grew to be team lead of the revenue development team. Wrote front-end code for handling signups, payments, optimization of the payment funnel, A/B testing, analytics and more.
- Oversaw a front-end payment funnel rewrite to simplify the checkout process for potential subscribers.
- Helped generate millions of dollars in revenue improvements while transitioning from Optimizely to an in-house solution for A/B testing and from Google Tag Manager to Segment for analytics.

NOVEMBER 2012-MAY 2016 Research Analyst Right Angle Sports

- Aggregated statistical data from all over the web into Excel to help sports betting syndicate team make data-backed wagers that influenced the market.
- Researched and analyzed teams and coaches from minimally covered conferences & leagues to find potential market advantages.

EDUCATION

Austin Coding Academy, Austin, Texas

April 2016

• Took 14 months of night classes to learn software engineering fundamentals.

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) - Journalism Kansas State University, Manhattan, KS